[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
[smooth jazz music playing]
[non-English singing]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
This--
this minister attacked me.
This is not
part of our agreement.
- [shouting in Japanese]
- [shouting indistinctly]
Don't fucking touch me!
No! No! No!
[both grunting]
[thuds]
[both shouting]
- [breathing heavily]
Hey.
You need to watch this.
You watch it.
I can't sit through that again.
Jake, we must be methodical
and miss nothing.
Come on.
♪ ♪
[high-pitched voices]
Who gave you this tape?
I don't know.
[speaking Japanese]
This--
this minister attacked me.
That fucker.
That's one
of the two Tozawa thugs
who attacked me
at my house yesterday.
The man with your friend,
do you realize who that is?
Holy shit.
[speaking Japanese]
[tools whirring]
[pop music playing]
Shimoda-san.
[both speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
Sato, where are you?
And why is Kobayashi
in my club?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[both speaking Japanese]
- Oi!
[speaking Japanese]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
You know what to do.
Take this straight
to my editor,
get it published
as soon as possible.
I will reach out
to my contacts.
But Tozawa is very good
at making people disappear.
Maybe you should lay low.
At least till the story runs.
You just said
that he threatened
Junko and the kids.
I won't look into him specifically.
Whoever sent you that
also touched this.
I'll try and lift a print
and see if I can find out
who sent it.
Beyond that, this will be
impossible to ignore.
And then I will arrest
Tozawa personally.
You make it public.
I'll take it from there.
I still can't help but feel
if I hadn't have screwed up
that airport raid, that Tozawa
would already be arrested
and Polina would have
never gotten on that boat.
Jake.
[upbeat pop music]
- [singing in Japanese]
[phone ringing]
[elevator dings]
[speaking Japanese]
[monitor beeping]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- [speaking Japanese]
[indistinct shouting]
[shouting in Japanese]
[all grunting]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[engine turns over]
[tires squealing]
[speaking Japanese]
- Hai.
- [speaking Japanese]
[line beeps]
- Hey, me again.
I haven't heard from you
since yesterday.
I talked to Polina's roommate.
Still nothing.
Seriously, Jake, if you have
any news on Polina,
call me, please.
- [speaking Japanese]
Everyone is talking
about the girl on the tape.
You knew her, right?
I told you
not to ask about that.
It's fine.
I knew her, yeah.
If there's anything
we can do, let us know.
Yes.
Iiyo.
If Tozawa's name is on it...
Then he goes in the article.
Ozaki got us an appointment
with the Vice Minister
Shigematsu in the morning.
- We can't wait that long.
- We don't have a choice.
Go home and get some rest.
both: Hai.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- [speaking Japanese]
I wasn't bribing him.
I was trying to back-foot him,
so that he would
give us Tozawa.
Jake, you asked
a government official
for information in exchange
for going easy on him.
It was a calculated risk.
Like with the loan officer,
Sugita?
How well did that go?
Do you want another suicide
on your hands?
That's a low blow.
Maruyama-san, if we can connect
Polina's murder to Tozawa,
why shouldn't we press
that angle?
Because we don't have Tozawa.
We have the vice minister,
one nameless Yakuza,
and another missing woman
presumed dead
who deserves to have
her story told.
[vending machine beeps]
[can clatters]
Katagiri-san.
[speaking Japanese]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
I wanted you
to have that back.
I--I didn't call earlier
because I didn't want it
to be true.
I'm so sorry.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Did they find her body?
No, not yet.
They're still looking.
I promise you, Sam, people will
know what they did to her.
♪ ♪
Do you want to get
a cup of coffee or something?
I want to be alone.
I was actually hoping
that you could tell me
a little bit about her.
What do you mean?
Polina.
Like, where she's from.
What brought her here.
I want to do right by her.
In the article.
She deserves that.
You came here
to interview me for a story?
No. No.
I just--I don't want
people to see her
as another faceless victim,
you know what I mean?
People should know
the funny, the kind...
- Oh, my God.
- Person that she was.
You couldn't wait a day
before coming to me with this?
Sam, whatever story
is gonna run,
it's coming out tomorrow.
So this is our only chance to--
- Get out of my fucking club.
[phone ringing]
Listen,
the boat is not registered
under any known associates
of Tozawa,
so it took a while.
But I got the name.
Who is it?
Someone named
Misaki Taniguchi.
Okay, thanks.
I'll look into it.
[speaking Japanese]
[train rattling]
[suspenseful music]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
[television static crackling]
[knocking]
[locks click]
Misaki.
Jake. You cannot be here.
I made sure nobody saw me.
I made sure of it.
I need to talk to you
about something.
What happened to you?
Oh, it's nothing.
Occupational hazard.
Did he do this because of me?
What do you know
about the Yoshino?
I don't know what that is.
It's Tozawa's boat.
Girls go on it
entertaining men for money.
A woman I know just went,
and she was killed.
Jake, I am so sorry.
Misaki, you're listed
as the owner of this boat.
That's impossible.
Well, your signature
is on the registry.
Then someone forged it.
I don't know
anything about this.
He shares nothing with me.
I'm gonna have
to write about this.
It's your name.
You're connected to Tozawa,
which connects him to the boat.
If you publish my name,
any future I might have had
beyond Tozawa
will be impossible.
So is there any other info
you can get from him?
Anything other than you
that connects him to the boat?
He isn't here.
He left his hotel.
Two nights ago.
He flew off somewhere.
Where?
When is he coming back?
I don't know.
I told you,
he tells me nothing.
[sighs]
Jake, you must
leave me out of it.
♪ ♪
Please.
[camera shutter clicking]
[speaking Japanese]
Oi.
[lighter clicking]
- [speaking Japanese]
[phone buzzing]
Hey, it's me again.
Where are you?
I need--I really need
to see you tonight.
Call me.
[speaking Japanese]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Oi!
[softly cheering]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[door slams]
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
[speaking Japanese]
[line beeps]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[keyboard clacking]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking Japanese]
[pop music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
[touch tones beeping]
- [speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[touch tones beeping]
- [speaking Japanese]
Hey, Mama-san Erika.
It's your former
number one girl.
I know it's been a while.
I just thought--
you free tonight?
Call me back.
[pop music playing]
Did you hear?
Jake's article connects
Tozawa to Yoshino.
The boat is registered
to his mistress.
Really?
How did you find out
the name on the registry
was a mistress?
It's a long story, but...
the important thing is,
we're gonna nail Tozawa.
[glasses clink]
I wonder what he'll do to her
when the article comes out.
Let's talk about something
other than work?
Sure.
I have started baking.
Cakes, pastries, petit fours.
- [laughs]
- You have an oven?
Of course not.
But my parents do.
I find it relieves stress.
Do you have one of the things
that squeezes filling
into pastry?
They are called piping bags.
And I have several.
[phone ringing]
Okay--okay.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[coughing]
[people speaking Japanese]
Jake.
What the hell happened?
They think
someone left a cigarette
burning in an ashtray.
It all went up in flames.
But they made copies
of the videotape, right?
They were all in that safe.
Everything inside melted
from the heat.
We can still run
the article, right?
Without that tape,
anything written about him
is libel.
We would be sued,
and we would lose.
No--no article?
What, the vice minister
just gets off scot-free?
You know
this wasn't an accident, right?
What, this all just happened
to be destroyed today?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[yells]
Fuck!
♪ ♪
[car door slams]
[groaning]
[pop music]
[speaking Japanese]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[touch tones beeping]
Erika, it's me again.
I should've said--
I owe you an apology.
I know.
I disappeared. I'm sorry.
Can I see you tonight?
I just need to see somebody
tonight who knows me.
[speaking Japanese]
Call me back.
Beautiful girl, good evening.
Get the fuck off me.
Fuck you.
Fuck this place.
Hey, do not go
in that host club.
Those guys are evil.
They'll take your money.
They'll all take your money.
They'll ruin your life.
- Get the fuck off me.
- Oi!
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[distant dog barking]
No tape, no story.
No accident.
Tozawa is...
an octopus.
Tentacles extending everywhere.
Cut off one,
another grows in its place.
But you know what happened.
You can look into it.
I cannot.
Are you serious?
I've been told officially
that the investigation
ends here.
But why?
[sighs]
What I'm going to tell you,
you will never write,
never repeat.
♪ ♪
We were building
a case together
against Tozawa in secret.
The octopus found out.
Miyamoto's death was made
to look like an overdose,
but Tozawa is responsible.
That son of a bitch.
That's sick.
Trust me.
Our day to get Tozawa
will come.
But for now, we wait.
And do what?
You did not come to Tokyo
in pursuit of one man.
There are other stories,
other crimes to be exposed.
That is your job, is it not?
♪ ♪
[shouting]
[grunting]
[yelling]
♪ ♪
[groaning]
[sighs]
Hai.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Oi!
[speaking Japanese]
[dance music playing]
[crowd cheering]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
[speaking Japanese]
No.
Hai.
No, I'd rather be here
and do some work.
Jake-san, did you hear
Miyamoto was found dead today?
Yeah, I just heard.
The police are saying
it was a heart attack.
But a source of mine
just told me,
he hears there's much more
to his death.
Like what?
I'm going to find out.
He did have
serious heart issues.
He told me a few times
that he had
ventricular arrhythmia.
Yeah, it was a thing my dad
always said was a real killer.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Miyamoto was
pretty shaken up about it.
He said he needed
to change his life.
I see.
Sorry, man.
It would have made
a great story.
Thank you.
[steady jazz music]
♪ ♪
[somber music]
Samantha!
Come on.
Don't be slowpoke.
[laughs]
You got this.
- [breathing heavily]
[laughs]
[groans]
You are a terrible person.
Whoo!
- [laughs]
[wind chimes jingling]
So I am 10, 11,
the age you get animal
as responsibility.
But mine was a sheep.
I named her Bela,
which means white.
- That's very cute.
- Thank you.
So one night, my grandfather
ties Bela to a tree,
and he gives me a long gun.
And he sits me
maybe 20 meters away.
Oh, no.
He made you shoot--
No, listen.
So my grandfather says,
"Stay up all night.
If bear or wolf comes,
you protect her."
And he goes back inside bed.
- What'd you do?
- Girl, what do you think?
I stay awake.
[chuckles]
But then,
3:00 in the morning, wolf.
- Yeah?
- Bang. I shoot.
I miss.
- [gasps]
- And wolf jump at my Bela.
- Fuck!
But then bang,
another gun behind me,
and wolf is dead.
[gasps]
I look,
and there's my grandfather,
all night in secret
20 meters behind me.
And he says,
"Polina, don't ever miss."
And then he beat
the shit out of me.
- Oh, that is awful.
- No.
Best lesson I ever got.
I'll never forget.
But same for you.
You see wolf,
you better not miss shot.
Seriously,
don't ever fucking miss.
I won't, I promise.
I will never fucking miss.
- Good.
You think
you'll ever go back?
No, never.
You?
There's nothing
to go back to.
What about your family?
I don't have a family.
Yes, you do.
You have me.
♪ ♪
[laughs]
[crying]
♪ ♪
[water running]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[groaning]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪